{"data":[{"question":"There are many of the ___ cosmetics in the department store.","a":"later","b":"last","c":"latter","d":"latest","answer":"4","explain":".\n- Latest (+noun): the most recent or the newest\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"It is _________ difficult to complete the project in time.","a":"fairly too","b":"rather","c":"quite too","d":"pretty too","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Fairly+ adjective\/adverb: more than a little, but much less than very \n- Rather, fairly, quite, and pretty are all used to say that something is true to some degree, but not completely or extremely \n+Rather is fairly formal but can be used in spoken English, especially British English. In American English it is more usual to use pretty. \n+Quite: can also be used in front of an adjective or adverb, and in British English a verb, to mean 'completely' ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"A customer wants something ___ bigger than this one.","a":"very","b":"fairly","c":"quite","d":"further","answer":"3","explain":".\n- Fairly+ adjective\/adverb:  more than a little, but much less than very\n- Rather, fairly, quite, and pretty are all used to say that something is true to some degree, but not completely or extremely\n+Rather is fairly formal but can be used in spoken English, especially British English. In American English it is more usual to use pretty.\n-Quite: can also be used in front of an adjective or adverb, and in British English a verb, to mean 'completely'\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"These slaves all looked _________ at their master and felt quite ___.","a":"sadly, sadly","b":"sad, sad","c":"sadly, sad","d":"sad, sadly","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Verb of appearance: (feel, taste, smell, sound, look, appear, and seem)+ Adjective : modifies the noun before the verb \n+ In this case, \"look\" is normal verb \n- \"Feel\" is appearance verb ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"___ the baby is learning to talk and walk!","a":"How slowly","b":"How slow","c":"What a slow way","d":"What a slow","answer":"1","explain":"\n- How [+ adjective\/adverb] used to emphasize the quality you are mentioning \n- Adverbs modify verbs, adjectives, and other adverbs: \"slowly\" (adv) describe \"learn\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"They are ___ little boys that they could not do the cleaning by themselves.","a":"such","b":"so","c":"less","d":"much","answer":"1","explain":"\n- So + adj + that \n- Such + noun phrase + that","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"We'll save you son as ___ as we can.","a":"many","b":"possible","c":"more","d":"much","answer":"4","explain":".\n- As much as: The same quantity as","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"All the hotels in the town were full up, so they stayed in a ___ inn.","a":"nearer","b":"nearly","c":"nearby","d":"near","answer":"3","explain":". \n- Nearby +noun: not far away","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"Wendy's ___ brother is two years ___ than she.","a":"elder, elder","b":"older, old","c":"elder, older","d":"older, older","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Old-older- oldest \n- (Especially brothers and sisters, is the one who was born first): elder\/eldest","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"},{"question":"The baby's ___ too young to express itself.","a":"yet","b":"quite","c":"very","d":"far","answer":"4","explain":".\n- Much\/far\/ rather\/a little\/a bit\/ a lot + adj: to emphasize adj\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"12","type":"1"}]}